Jenuel Ganawed

Web developer

La Trinidad 2601 jenuelganawed936@gmail.com 0950-325-5547

Hi! I'm Jenuel, and I am a Web Developer.

I enjoy creating things that live on the internet, whether that be websites, applications, or anything in between. My goal is to Join or Work in any opportunity that will help me grow in this Industry. I welcome challenging projects and enjoy working with all sorts of personalities.

Shortly after graduating from Kings College of The Philippines, I joined the team of software developers at a company where I work on a wide variety of fascinating technologies and helpful projects. Here are a few technologies I've been working with recently:

- JavaScript (ES6+)
- HTML & (S)CSS
- Vue
- laravel/Lumen
- AngularS
- Ruby on Rails
- Codelgniter

Work Experience

Software/Web Dev.

UTalk Philippines - Baguio September 2019 to Present

- Full-time software developer
- Worked with a variety of techs. such as Vue, Angular, Codelgniter, Lumen, Ruby on Rails, MySQL, MongoDB
- Maintaining the system of the company

Software/Web Dev.

Dap-ayan Eatery

August 2018 to May 2019

- Participated as an author and a project developer of their own private Ordering Management System
- Technologies used are MySQL, Codelgniter

Designer and Web Programmer

I Learn Skills Development Academy September 2018 to December 2018

- Created web designs for wonderful clients
- Maintaining their system as well as their website

Education

Bachelor's of Information Technology in Information Technology

Kings College of The Philippines May 2019

High School Diploma

Cordillera Career Development College March 2014

Skills

- Javascript
- Vue Js
- Angular Js
- Codelgniter
- Html & (S)CSS
- Laravel/Lumen
- Ruby On Rails

Links

http://jenuelganawed.ml

https://github.com/BroJenuel